

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Searching for a Junior Front End Developer position that allows me to implement my creative thinking and critical problem-solving skills using my design ability and knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript to execute and finalize

web applications

Consistently delivered quality designs in fast-paced, Creative Design

high-volume environments for digital and print

Developed and refined brand identity designs for use in web, email, digital and print while using the latest technologies

Effective Leadership Managed the design, proofing, printing and shipping of printed

materials for trade shows and clients

Nurtured professional relationships and created an experience

and atmosphere of trust

EMPLOYMENT

February 2019 - Present **National Multiple Sclerosis Society**

Web Production Specialist

Manages content for all National MS Society websites

Supports the development of new fundraising event websites

Serves as subject matter leader on DonorDrive, Luminate

and Kentico CMS

Develops and upholds best practices for web content using

HTML and CSS

April 2018 – January 2019 Arnold Printing

Web to Print Technician

Achieved near perfect file creation and edits in several different software program

Maximized split shift work load in small department

Coordinate with different departments and managers on enhancing the productively of work flow

Maintain and elevated printing standards of Arnold Printing

and of clients expectations

May 2014 - April 2018 **lacono Productions**

Print Technician

Earned praise from management for professional commutation with clients

Coordinated the development and update of company website

Managed and controlled file setup, printing and laminating/trimming of printed items

CONTACT





in james-tritt





jimtritt



jamestritt

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Graphic & Web Design

UI/UX Design

Website Development

Photography Branding Marketing

Illustrator **InDesign** Photoshop Lightroom Sketch

HTML5/CSS3

Email Design/Campaign

MailChimp **j**Query JavaScript Wordpress

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

Eagle Scout

Positive work ethic Creative thinker Eager to learn Hard worker Team player

Effective communicator

INTEREST/ACTIVITIES

Yoga

Running

Exploring

Traveling

Pod casts

Photography

EDUCATION

Cincinnati State

Cincinnati, Ohio - Associate of

Applied Science

June 2017 - Present

Web and Multimedia Design

Mount St. Joseph University

Cincinnati, Ohio - Bachelor of Fine Arts

Aug. 2008 -May 2013

Graphic Design - BFA Concentration in Photography - BA